{
    "subject": "resource/11:14",
    "predicate": "property/cinematography",
    "object": "resource/Shane_Hurlbut",
    "human_readable": "The cinematography of 11:14 is handled by Shane Hurlbut.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9252562522888184,
            "question": "Which film features the cinematography of Shane Hurlbut?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8726485371589661,
            "question": "What role does Shane Hurlbut play in the creation of films like 11:14?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8509014248847961,
            "question": "Who is the cinematographer for the film 11:14?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8144526481628418,
            "question": "Besides 11:14, what other projects might Shane Hurlbut have worked on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6564205288887024,
            "question": "Is Shane Hurlbut known for his work in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6377556324005127,
            "question": "Name a film by Shane Hurlbut."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46180009841918945,
            "question": "What is Shane Hurlbut's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27869415283203125,
            "question": "Can you give an example of another film with notable cinematography?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20164935290813446,
            "question": "What skills are required to be a successful cinematographer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18987365067005157,
            "question": "How does cinematography contribute to the overall impact of a film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The cinematography of 11:14 is handled by Shane Hurlbut.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1677_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What skills are required to be a successful cinematographer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1677_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of another film with notable cinematography?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1677_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Shane Hurlbut's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1677_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1677_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1677_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1677_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1677_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1677_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1677_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1677_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1677_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1677_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1677_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided documents do not mention a film titled \"11:14\" or any information about Shane Hurlbut working on such a project. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention the cinematography of a film called \"11:14\" or any work related to such a film. They all discuss the career and works of Shane Hurlbut, ASC, but none specifically reference a film titled \"11:14.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context, there is no mention of Shane Hurlbut being involved with the film \"11:14\". Therefore, the information in these documents does not support the statement that \"The cinematography of 11:14 is handled by Shane Hurlbut.\"\n\nResponse:\n```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Shane Hurlbut working on a film titled \"11:14\" in any of the provided context information.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention any project titled \"11:14\" or its cinematography. All the projects discussed are either completed films, series episodes, or upcoming productions that do not align with \"11:14\".",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}